<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
    <info>
        <name>AAA Sneaker</name>
        <description>All DEX skills + Artisan's Tools</description>
		<author url="https://github.com/cajadehu/aurorabuilder/">LemonCat</author>
		<update version="0.0.3">
            <file name="background-sneaker.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cajadehu/aurorabuilder/main/background-sneaker.xml" />
        </update>
    </info>
    <element name="AAA Sneaker" type="Background" source="AAA" id="ID_BACKGROUND_AAA_SNEAKER">
        <description>
            <p>You have spent much of your childhood tiptoeing around hallways, peeking through keyholes, hiding in shadows, and listening in on others conversations.</p>
            <p class="indent">You might have been working as a spy, gathering secrets and intel for your Patron. Perhaps you were a burglar, or a lookout for a gang. Maybe you just love gossip!</p>
			<ul class="unstyled">
				<li><strong>Skill Proficiencies:</strong>Acrobatics, Sleight of Hand, Stealth.</li>
				<li><strong>Tool Proficiencies:</strong>Thieves’ Tools, Artisan's Tools.</li>
				<li><strong>Languages:</strong> Thieves’ Cant</li>
			</ul>
        </description>
        <setters>
            <set name="short">Acrobatics, Sleight of Hand, Stealth, Thieves’ Tools, Artisan's Tools, Thieves’ Cant</set>
        </setters>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_SKILL_ACROBATICS" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_SKILL_SLEIGHTOFHAND" />
			<grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_SKILL_STEALTH" />
			<grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_TOOL_PROFICIENCY_THIEVES_TOOLS" />
			<select type="Proficiency" name="Tool Proficiency (Sneaker)" supports="Artisan tools"/>
            <grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_ROGUE_THIEVES_CANT" />
			
            <select type="List" name="Personality Trait" number="2">
                <item id="1">Gloomy. Death waits for us all. It is just a matter of time.</item>
                <item id="2">Anxious. What if it rains, and I slip in the mud, and break my ankle? AAHH!</item>
                <item id="3">Haggler. Hmm, the guy down the street is selling these for 5cp less.</item>
                <item id="4">Gormand. This could use a little more salt to balance the flavors. 3 stars.</item>
                <item id="5">Rude. Were you born stupid or have you been practicing? Should I use smaller words?</item>
                <item id="6">Creepy. Your hair smells even better when you're awake.</item>
                <item id="7">Peppy. C'mon guys! Rise and shine! Adventure awaits!</item>
                <item id="8">Vain. Do my boots match my gloves? Isn't my hair silky smooth?</item>
            </select>
            <select type="List" name="Ideal">
                <item id="1">I will see justice done, regardless of circumstances. (Lawful)</item>
                <item id="2">Life is meant to be fun! (Chaotic)</item>
                <item id="3">I help the poor and downtrodden when I can. (Good)</item>
                <item id="4">Power is it's own reward. (Evil)</item>
                <item id="5">I am but a leaf on the river of life. (Neutral)</item>
                <item id="6">The world just needs more love and understanding. (Good)</item>
            </select>
            <select type="List" name="Bond">
                <item id="1">My Clan's holy relic was taken. I must retrieve it no matter the cost.</item>
                <item id="2">To asure a place of honor in the afterlife, I must accomplish a great feat.</item>
                <item id="3">I need a title to wed my beloved.</item>
                <item id="4">I escaped a death cult as a child. I pray they never find me.</item>
                <item id="5">I was framed for a crime I didn't commit.</item>
                <item id="6">I will avenge the murder of my family.</item>
            </select>
            <select type="List" name="Flaw">
                <item id="1">It's how much? Nevermind. By the way, when do you close?</item>
                <item id="2">It wasn't my fault. Honest. Okay, maybe it was.</item>
                <item id="3">I am completely focused on what you are saying OOH! A BIRD!</item>
                <item id="4">Pranks and practical jokes are the highest form of humor.</item>
                <item id="5">I think you mean "whom", not "who". How do you not know this.</item>
                <item id="6">I bite my toenails and pick my nose in public.</item>
            </select>
        </rules>
    </element>
</elements>